One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Zero Escape
‫لا مفر‬
It can't be.
‫محال‬
No... No...
‫...مستحيل... مستحيل‬
Pedro-san sacrificed himself...
‫...بيدرو-سان قد ضحى بحياته‬
If only we were... if only we were...!
‫...لو أننا كنا أكثر... أكثر‬
If only we were stronger...
‫...أكثر قوة‬
Our enemies are the ones who should be crying.
‫دعوا البكاء لأعدائنا‬
We cannot allow ourselves to be upset.
‫يجب ألّا نفقد رباطة جأشنا‬
Hey, Jinbe-san !
‫مهلًا يا جينبي-سان‬
How could you say something so cruel?!
‫كيف تخبرنا بهذا بكل برود؟‬
Just because you spent the least amount of time with Pedro doesn't mean that–
‫...فأنت لم تعرف بيدرو-سان بقدرنا‬
I'm just saying that we shouldn't let our guards down!
‫أنا أطلب منكم ألّا تفقدوا تركيزكم‬
We had our backs against the wall on that coastline...
‫كنا في وضعٍ حرج عند الساحل‬
Pedro knew that we were in a dangerous situation and was prepared to sacrifice himself whenever necessary.
‫قرر التضحية بنفسه لأنّه أدرك مدى خطورة الوضع‬
This is...
‫...هذا‬
Pedro's victory!
‫نصر بيدرو‬
This is an unprecedented series of events for them!
‫إنّها خسارات ذريعة وغير مسبوقة بالنسبة لهم‬
Your strength really drove Big Mom into a corner!
‫قوتكم دفعت بيغ مام إلى الهاوية‬
"Keep going!"
‫امضوا قدمًا»؟»‬
Luffy understood the stakes instantly...
‫...شعر لوفي بذلك فورًا‬
and decided to take the enemy on all by himself.
‫وقرر مواجهة العدو وحده‬
Katakuri has a bounty of over one billion! It's an all or nothing situation.
‫مكافأة كاتاكوري تفوق المليار إنّها مواجهة بعنوان أكون أو لا أكون‬
We are still in Totto Land!
‫ما زلنا في الإقليم البحري لتوتولاند‬
Sooner or later, the pirate queen of this country, Big Mom, will be on our tail!
‫لذا ستطاردنا ملكة قراصنة هذه البلاد بيغ مام قريبًا‬
And her fleet could close in on us from all directions at any time!
‫وقد يُحيط بنا أسطولها من جميع الاتجاهات في أي لحظة‬
So until we escape from Big Mom's territory...
‫...لذا ريثما تخرجون من منطقة بيغ مام‬
we must not let down our guard! Don't you hear Pedro saying that?!
‫حريّ بكم ألّا تفقدوا تركيزكم أليس هذا ما يقوله بيدرو داخلكم؟‬
I'm very sorry.
‫أقدّم خالص اعتذاري‬
I was way out of line.
‫فأنا لم أتمالك نفسي‬
Nami, give us directions!
‫نامي، زودينا بالتعليمات‬
Okay!
‫أجل‬
Sanji-kun and the others will be sailing to us from Cacao Island,
‫سيأتينا سانجي-كن والآخرون من جزيرة الكاكاو‬
so we need to make sure we don't miss them.
‫لذا لا نريد أن نفوّت مقابلتهم‬
There's a strong wind coming! It's a tailwind!
‫ستهب رياح قوية قريبًا، وهي رياح خلفية‬
So, steer to starboard!
‫لذا توجه نحو الميمنة‬
Hard a-starboard!
‫أقصى الميمنة‬
We'll catch the wind on the starboard side and head straight west!
‫لنستغل الرياح في جانب الميمنة ونتجه للغرب مباشرة‬
We'll take a direct route!
‫سنسلك الطريق الأقصر‬
Roger!
‫عُلم‬
I'll go refill the cola we used!
‫سأعيد تعبئة الكولا التي استعملناها للتو‬
I'll watch for enemies!
‫سأتولى المراقبة‬
Okay!
‫حسنًا‬
I'm in position!
‫أنا في مركزي‬
Uh-huh!
‫أجل‬
I'll help you monitor the sea currents!
‫دعوا لي مراقبة التيارات‬
They're coming from six o'clock!
‫إنّهم قادمون باتجاه الساعة السادسة‬
There's a person?!
‫شخص؟‬
I-It can't be!
‫مـ-محال‬
Cake!
‫كعكة‬
It can't be... that can't... that can't be possible!
‫محال، هذا... هذا غير معقول‬
Big Mom is walking on the water!
‫بيغ مام تسير على الماء‬
No way! That's ridiculous!
‫محال، كيف يُعقل ذلك؟‬
It's not water... It's...
‫...تلك ليست مياه، بل‬
candy?!
‫حلوى؟‬
She's walking on a large blob of moving candy!
‫إنّها تسير على كتلة ضخمة من الحلوى المتحركة‬
Using candy?!
‫تستخدم الحلوى؟‬
Hey, does that mean...?
‫...مهلًا، أيعني ذلك‬
The only person capable of producing that...
‫...الشخص الوحيد القادر على صنعها‬
It must be... him !
‫لا بدّ أنّه الفاعل‬
Lick...
‫بيرورين‬
Candy Sea Slug!
‫حلوى محار البحر‬ ‫«آمي آومي أوشي»‬
Where did Zeus go?
‫أين ذهب زيوس؟‬
It's his job to help Mama cross the sea!
‫من واجبه حمل ماما عبر البحر‬
It can't be...
‫محال‬
But I suppose that's fine... because I have a score to settle with them!
‫على كلٍّ، لدي دافع قوي الآن للنيل منهم‬
Pedro sacrificed his own life!
‫بيدرو ضحّى بحياته من أجل التخلّص منه‬
I'll remember... that jaguar mink's face!
‫سأتذكر وجه فهد المينك البغيض ذاك‬
Isn't that right, Napoleon? There's nothing more humiliating!
‫ألستُ محقًّا يا نابليون؟ لا شيء أكثر إذلالًا من ذلك‬
It is a grievous crime in this land.
‫طاقم قبعة القش تعدوا حدود الإجرام في أرضنا‬
The Straw Hats have no future here.
‫لا مستقبل لهم بعد الآن‬
How should I torment...
‫...إذًا كيف‬
his companions to sate my rage?!
‫أعذّبُ رفاقه حتّى أشعر بالرضا؟‬
Whole Cake Island
‫جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة‬
Everyone's gone!
‫أين رحل الجميع؟‬
I really wanna eat some flames! I'm losing my strength...
‫...أود تناول النيران بسرعة، إني أفقد قواي‬
I wanna eat thunderclouds, too...
‫...أنا أيضًا أود تناول السحب الرعدية‬
At Sea Within the Borders of Totto Land
‫في البحر داخل حدود توتولاند‬
Oh... So Lola-chan, who we met at Thriller Bark, was a master at making chocolate?!
‫ماذا؟ إذًا كانت لولا-تشان من ثريلر بارك خبيرة في إعداد الشوكولاتة؟‬
That's right. Lola was the minister of chocolate on Cacao Island,
‫أجل، كانت لولا وزيرة الشوكولاتة في جزيرة الكاكاو‬
but after she left, the position was never filled!
‫لكن ذلك المنصب بقي شاغرًا منذ مغادرتها‬
Oh, how come?
‫ما السبب إذًا؟‬
Because the presumed candidate here keeps rejecting the position.
‫لأنّ المرشحة الأبرز بين الجميع هنا رفضت العرض‬
Isn't that right, Pudding?
‫أليس كذلك يا بودينغ؟‬
B-Because, to me...
‫...ذ-ذلك لأنني‬
the only minister of chocolate for Chocolat Town should be Sister Lola!
‫أعتبر أختي الكبيرة لولا هي وزيرة الشوكولاتة الوحيدة لبلدة الشوكولاتة‬
And I've always hoped that she would return someday...
‫وأتمنى أن تعود يومًا ما‬
I know how you feel, but...
‫...أتفهم شعوركِ، لكن‬
Could I be mistaken?
‫أأنا مخطئ؟‬
No...
‫...كلا‬
Pound Father of Lola and Chiffon
‫باوند (والد لولا وشيفون)‬
I-I think that's my daughter!
‫أ-أظن أنّها ابنتي‬
Hey! Hey!
‫أنتِ، أنتِ‬
Hey!
‫أنتِ‬
She's gone now...
‫لقد رحلت‬
Chiffon...
‫...شيفون‬
Hey! Come out from under there, Pudding!
‫بحقكِ، أخرجي من عندكِ يا بودينغ‬
N-No way!
‫كـ-كفاكِ مزاحًا‬
I'm wearing a wedding dress right now!
‫إنني أرتدي فستان الزفاف حاليًّا‬
If I sit on the carpet with that man,
‫لذا إن جلستُ على السجادة بجوار هذا الرجل‬
people will think that we just got married to each other!
‫فسيظنون أننا عروسين جديدين أقاما حفل زفافهما للتو‬
What people?
‫من هم؟‬
You never know who's watching! And I'll be annoyed if they think it!
‫لا تعرفين من قد يرانا، ويزعجني إن ظنّوا ذلك‬
It.. It'll... It'll really annoy me, okay?!
‫هذا... هـ-هذا يزعجني، أفهمتِ؟‬
Sorry about the trouble. Just don't fall, okay?
‫يؤسفني ذلك، لكن لا تسقطي‬
Sh-Shut up!
‫ا-اخرس‬
Oh! What a sweet man! He's worried about me!
‫يا له من طيّب، إنّه قلقٌ عليّ‬
Who do you think you are?! Whether I fall or not isn't your business!
‫بحقك، من تظن نفسك؟ سقوطي من عدمه ليس من شأنك‬
There's Cacao Island!
‫بوسعي رؤية جزيرة الكاكاو‬
All right! Let's start making the cake as soon as we arrive!
‫عظيم، لنبدأ بإعداد الكعكة فور وصولنا‬
Hey! Did you hear what I said, Sanji...
‫...انتظر، هل سمعت ما قلته يا سانجي‬
-san ?!
‫سان؟-‬
Mirro-world
‫عالم المرايا‬
What an idiot!
‫يا له من أحمق‬
I can't believe he broke the mirror himself!
‫لقد حطّم المرآة بنفسه‬
Are you trying to sacrifice yourself to let your friends escape?!
‫أتحاول التضحية بنفسك ليتسنّى لرفاقك الهرب؟‬
I'm gonna kick your ass!
‫سوف أُبرحك ضربًا‬
Don't be ridiculous!
‫كفاك هراءً‬
Who do you think you're talking to?!
‫من تخاطب برأيك؟‬
Commander Katakuri has a bounty of one billion, fifty-seven million belly!
‫تبلغ مكافأة كاتاكوري-ساما مليار و57 مليون بيري‬
He's the strongest of the Three Sweet Commanders!
‫إنّه أقوى قادة الحلوى الثلاث‬
Hawk Gatling!
‫هوك غاتلينغ‬ ‫رشاش الصقر‬
I'm following your lead on this...
‫إنني أجاريك في تحركاتك‬
Am I doing it wrong?
‫هل أنفذها بشكل خاطئ؟‬
But... it's more efficient this way!
‫لكنها أكثر فاعلية بهذه الطريقة‬
That's Commander Katakuri for you!
‫كما هو متوقع من كاتاكوري-ساما‬
Commander Katakuri, that's so brutal!
‫ذلك قاسٍ يا كاتاكوري-ساما‬
I suppose you understand now.
‫أظن أنّك أدركت الآن‬
As I already told you... in terms of ability...
‫...كما أخبرتك سابقًا، من حيث القدرة‬
there's nothing you can do that I cannot.
‫ليس هنالك شيء يمكنك القيام به ولا يمكنني فعله‬
I have you beat in both speed and strength.
‫أنت أدنى مستوى منّي في السرعة والقوة‬
Rubber won't lose to mochi !
‫لن يخسر المطاط أمام كعكة موتشي‬
I'm not gonna lose!
‫أنا لن أخسر‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Hawk Stamp!
‫هوك ستامب‬ ‫ختم الصقر‬
Is that it?
‫أهذا كلّ شيء؟‬
No way!
‫ليس بعد‬
He disappeared again!
‫اختفى مجدّدًا‬
I knew Commander Katakuri was in a different league!
‫كما توقعت، إنّ كاتاكوري-ساما في مستوى مختلف عنه‬
So you're trying strength next?
‫إذًا محاولتك التالية هي القوة؟‬
Give up already.
‫استسلم فحسب‬
What a huge punch!
‫يا لها من قبضة ضخمة‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Elephant...
‫إيليفنت‬ ‫بندقية‬
Gun!
‫غن‬ ‫الفيل‬
Commander Katakuri's is even bigger!
‫قبضة كاتاكوري-ساما أضخم منها‬
Is that how you do...
‫هل نفذتُ ضربة «بندقية الفيل» بالشكل الصحيح؟‬
Cacao Island
‫جزيرة الكاكاو‬
She's so beautiful in her wedding dress!
‫يا لجمالها وهي ترتدي فستان زفافها‬
I feel bad for her. Her wedding was ruined.
‫يا لها من مسكينة، لقد أُفسد حفل زفافها‬
But even with that sad look, she's still so beautiful!
‫رغم ملامحها الحزينة إلّا أنّها ما زالت جميلة‬
Oh! It's the minister of puffs!
‫وزيرة المعجنات‬
M-Madam Chiffon!
‫شـ-شيفون-ساما‬
Everyone, don't worry! Sister Chiffon is not the primary culprit of the revolt!
‫اطمئنوا جميعًا، أختي شيفون لا علاقة لها في التمرد‬
The one at fault is her husband: Gang Bege!
‫الخطأ يقع على عاتق زوجها غانغ بيجي‬
I'm sorry, Sister.
‫المعذرة‬
I told them that I'd threaten you and force you to help me make the cake.
‫أخبرتهم أنني سأهددكِ وأرغمكِ على مساعدتي في إعداد الكعكة‬
That's okay, Pudding. That's the position I'm in now.
‫لا عليك يا بودينغ، هذا ما أنا عليه حاليًّا في نظر العامة‬
Who could've expected such a happy wedding
‫لا أحد توقع أنّ الزفاف السعيد سيفسده اقتحام قبعة القش لوفي وخيانة بيجي‬
That Sanji man ruined it, too!
‫وكذلك كان سانجي محتالًا للغاية‬
What's done is done.
‫لا حيلة لمنع ما حدث‬
Madam Pudding, I'm sure you're having a hard time!
‫بودينغ-ساما، لا بدّ أنّكِ تمرين بوقتٍ عصيب‬
Mama must be angry.
‫أتساءل ما مدى غضب ماما؟‬
Yes, she's mad and hungry.
‫أجل، إنّها غاضبة وجائعة‬
In addition, she's on a ravenous rampage and may very well destroy this country.
‫الأدهى من ذلك، إنّها تمر بنوبة جوع وقد تدمر الدولة‬
Oh, how horrible...
‫...يا له من أمر مرعب‬
Is everything ready?
‫أكل شيء جاهز؟‬
Yes! About an hour ago, the 31 most renowned chefs from Whole Cake Island arrived here.
‫أجل، منذ ساعة تقريبًا جاء 31 طاهٍ من جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة‬
Sweets Factory, Chocolat Town
‫مصنع الحلوى - بلدة الشوكولاتة‬
We've been expecting you, Madam Pudding!
‫كنا بانتظارك يا بودينغ-ساما‬
We're the 31 head chefs of Whole Cake Island!
‫نحن نخبة الطُهاة في جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة وعددنا 31‬
We're the WCI 31!
‫اختصارٌ لجزيرة الكعكة الكاملة WCI‬ ‫"WCI 31" نحن‬
Sister Chiffon and I will make the wedding cake that can stop Mama.
‫سنتولى أنا وأختي شيفون إعداد كعكة الزفاف التي ستوقف هيجان ماما‬
Please help us.
‫أرجو أن تمدوا لنا يد العون‬
Yes, ma'am! We've already made preparations!
‫حاضر، لقد بدأنا مسبقًا في التحضيرات‬
Madam Pudding was the bride, so she was affected the most by what happened...
‫كانت العروس بودينغ-ساما المتضرر الأكبر مما حدث‬
You can count on me! I'm not gonna let Mama destroy our country!
‫اعتمدوا عليّ، لن أدع ماما تدمّر الدولة‬
Madam Pudding!
‫بودينغ-ساما‬
I can't believe she's overcoming the pain and overseeing the cake-making herself!
‫لا أصدّق أنّها تجاوزت ألمها وقررت الإشراف على إعداد الكعكة بنفسها‬
She's literally a goddess of salvation!
‫إنّها منقذتنا فعلًا‬
Good luck!
‫ابذلي جهدكِ‬
Go ahead and go inside with Rabiyan.
‫اسبقيني للداخل برفقة رابيان يا أختي‬
Okay.
‫أجل‬
Please, everyone! Listen to me!
‫أرجو أن تصغوا إليّ جميعًا‬
I need you to do me a favor!
‫أريد أن تسدوني معروفًا بسيطًا‬
We're going to risk our lives and bake the cake that will determine the fate of our country!
‫سنخاطر بأرواحنا ونعد الكعكة التي ستغير مصير دولتنا‬
We really need to concentrate!
‫نحن بأمسّ الحاجة إلى التركيز‬
So, please don't look inside the factory under any circumstance while we're at it!
‫لذا لا تنظروا أبدًا إلى داخل المصنع أثناء تواجدنا فيه‬
Yes, ma'am!
‫حاضر‬
And no matter who it is, don't let anyone look inside!
‫وأيضًا، لا تسمحوا لأيّ شخص بالنظر إلى الداخل كائنًا من كان‬
We understand, Madam Pudding!
‫مفهوم يا بودينغ-ساما‬
Thank you, everyone!
‫شكرًا لكم جميعًا‬
Good luck, Madam Pudding!
‫ابذلي جهدكِ يا بودينغ-ساما‬
This way, they won't see Sanji-san...
‫لن يكتشفوا أمر سانجي-سان بهذا الحال‬
And now, I've got to deal with the ones who will be helping us.
‫تبقى تولّي أمر العاملين معنا‬
Head Chefs! Come inside one at a time!
‫رؤساء الطهاة، ادخلوا واحدًا تلو الآخر‬
Head chef of the First Kitchen, Buche, reporting for duty.
‫رئيس طهاة المطبخ الأول بوش يتقدم للدخول‬
Stay still.
‫لا تتحرك‬
I'm gonna modify your memories...
‫سأعدّل ذكرياتك‬
Edit!
‫إيدت‬ ‫تعديل‬
Hey, let me down.
‫أنزلني‬
Okay!
‫حاضر‬
Here you go!
‫ها أنت ذا‬
That must've been a tough ride.
‫أحسنت صنعًا‬
Inside the Factory
‫داخل المصنع‬
We don't have much time,
‫الوقت يُداهمنا، لذا رسمتُ مخطط لكعكة الزفاف في الطريق‬
What?! You memorized it?
‫ماذا؟ هل تتذكرها؟‬
Pretty much.
‫بكل دقة‬
No way! It's easy to remember the shape, but how could you know the ingredients without tasting it?!
‫محال، ربما تتذكر شكلها لكن كيف عرفت مكوناتها من دون تذوقها حتّى؟‬
By smelling it.
‫من الرائحة‬
Seriously?!
‫بجدية؟‬
Now, hurry up! Every minute counts!
‫والآن دعونا نُسرع، فكل دقيقة ذات أهمية بالغة‬
Pudding-chan's chef outfit is so cute!
‫بودينغ-تشان تبدو فاتنة حتّى في رداء الطهاة‬
Madam Pudding, are you all right?!
‫بودينغ-ساما، أأنتِ بخير؟‬
Let's do it, Sir Husband!
‫لنبذل جهدنا يا سيدي المتزوج‬
Huh? Me?
‫ماذا؟ أنا؟‬
Come here!
‫تعال‬
I took out their memories of the incident earlier...
‫عدلتُ على ذكريات الطهاة عن الحادثة‬
In other words, they think the wedding finished without a hitch, and...
‫أي أنّهم يظنون أنّ الزفاف جرى كما ينبغي‬
that w... we are... m... married!
‫و-ونحن... مـ-متزوجان‬
But...
‫...ولكن‬
they think the wedding cake was ruined by unexpected weather
‫لقد أُفسدت كعكة الزفاف بسبب هطول أمطار غير متوقعة‬
and that Mama was enraged, so the cake has to be remade quickly.
‫مما أثار غضب ماما، لذا علينا الإسراع لإعداد الكعكة مجدّدًا‬
That is what they believe now.
‫هذا ما أعدتُ كتابته في ذكرياتهم‬
I see.
‫فهمت‬
Their memories of making the cake are still fresh, so they'll be useful to us!
‫ما تزال ذكرياتهم عن إعداد الكعكة الأولى سليمة مما سيساعدنا في إعدادها مجدّدًا‬
Who drew this blueprint and recipe for the wedding cake?!
‫من عمل هذا المخطط ووصفة كعكة الزفاف؟‬
Me!
‫أنا‬
Sir Husband, you drew this?!
‫سيدي المتزوج، أأنت من كتبها؟‬
Yeah. Let me know if there are any mistakes.
‫أجل، أخبروني إن وجدتم أي أخطاء‬
It's perfect!
‫إنّها مثالية‬
You even identified the hidden flavors
‫حتّى أنّك اكتشفت المكونات السرية التي استغرق رئيس الطهاة سترويزن أسبوعًا لإعدادها‬
I heard rumors you were skilled, but wow, you're amazing!
‫رغم أنني سمعتُ أنّك ماهر، إلّا أنّك فقت توقعاتي‬
And by an odd coincidence, as husband and wife...
‫...وبصفتكما زوجان، فإنّ إعداد هذه الكعكة سوف‬
Husband and wife?!
‫زوجان؟‬
..this cake will be your first project, strangely enough.
‫يكون تعاونكما الأول‬
Yeah, you're right. I'm a little embarrassed.
‫أجل، أشعر بالإحراج‬
Husband and wife...
‫...زوجان‬
Are you okay, Madam Wife?!
‫ما الخطب سيدتي الزوجة؟‬
W... Wife...
‫...ز-زوجة‬
Madam Wife!
‫سيدتي الزوجة؟‬
W...
‫...زوجـ‬
Madam Wife! Madam Wife!
‫سيدتي الزوجة؟ سيدتي الزوجة؟‬
W-W...
‫...زوجـ... زوجـ‬
Stay with us, Mada–
‫...تماسكي يا سيدتي الزو‬
Stop! She'll die!
‫توقف، ستموت‬
He called us husband and wife! Oh my!
‫لقد دعانا بالزوجين‬
Hey!
‫أنتِ‬
What? He suddenly said "Hey" to me!
‫«ماذا؟ قال لي فجأة «أنتِ‬
Maybe it's not so bad to have an assertive husband...
‫امتلاك زوج حازم قد لا تكون فكرة سيئة‬
No, but it's important to start things right.
‫لكن يجب أن تكون البدايات جيّدة‬
I-If you act like my master, I'll kill you, Sanji...
‫...إ-إن تصرفتَ وكأنّك قوامٌ علي، فسأقتلك يا سانجي‬
I need you to gather these as fast as you can.
‫أريد بعض المكونات بسرعة‬
Non-homogenized milk, sugar beets, bananas, black sesame,
‫حليب، شمندر السكر، موز، سمسم أسود‬
roasted soy flour, yogurt. A lot of it.
‫دقيق صويا محمص، والكثير من اللبن‬
Yes, sir!
‫حاضر‬
...-san !
‫سان-‬
Everyone! It's a race against time until the cake is complete!
‫جميعًا، هذا سباق مع الوقت حتّى تكتمل الكعكة‬
Chiffon-chan, you bake the giant chiffon cake.
‫ستعد شيفون-تشان كعكة شيفون الضخمة‬
Pudding-chan, you handle all the chocolate tempering.
‫ستتولّى بودينغ-تشان أمر إذابة الشوكولاتة‬
You have two hours and 40 minutes!
‫لديكما ساعتان و40 دقيقة‬
It certainly is a fight against time.
‫إنّه سباق مع الوقت فعلًا‬
When we get there, I'll add my secret ingredient!
‫عندما نصل إلى تلك اللحظة، سأضيف مكوناتي السرية‬
I'll make you taste true sweetness!
‫سأجعلكم ترون ماهية الحلوى الحقيقية‬
T-True sweetness?!
‫الـ-الحلوى الحقيقية؟‬
In three hours, we'll load the incomplete cake on a ship and leave Cacao Island.
‫بعد ثلاث ساعات، سنحمل الكعكة الغير مكتملة على سفينة ونغادر جزيرة الكاكاو‬
Whole Cake Island Chocolat Town Cacao Island
‫جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة‬ ‫بلدة الشوكولاتة جزيرة الكاكاو‬
And as we let it cool down, we'll decorate it on the ship.
‫وبينما ندعها تبرد، سنزيّنها على السفينة‬
Before we return to the Sunny where Luffy and the others are being chased by Big Mom,
‫قبل أن نلتقي بلوفي والآخرين المطاردين من قبل بيغ مام وهم على متن سفينة الساني‬
we'll finish making the greatest cake ever!
‫سننهي إعداد أروع كعكة على الإطلاق‬
I see. That sounds efficient.
‫فهمت، تبدو عملية مُحكمة‬
But at that fast of a pace?
‫لكن كيف سننجز ذلك بهذه السرعة؟‬
No matter how you look at it, that's impossible!
‫إنّها مستحيلة مهما حاولت‬
We gotta do it! Do you want Mama to destroy the country?!
‫يجب أن نفعلها، أتودون أن تدمر ماما الدولة؟‬
I'm sorry! We'll follow you!
‫المعذرة، سنبذل ما بوسعنا‬
All right!
‫عظيم‬
Let's start baking!
‫لنشرع في إعدادها‬
For those who saved Lola!
‫من أجل منقذين لولا‬
For Sanji-san !
‫من أجل سانجي-سان‬
I'll make my special extremely-fluffy chiffon cake!
‫سأعد كعكة شيفون الطرية خاصّتي‬
I must help Sanji-san and the others get away!
‫سأساعد سانجي-سان ورفاقه على الهرب‬
With my very sweet chocolate!
‫من خلال الشوكولاتة الحلوة خاصّتي‬
Keep hanging on, guys!
‫اصمدوا يا رفاق‬
I'll show them!
‫...سأريهم‬
My offensive cooking!
‫الطبخ على أصوله‬
Mirro-world
‫عالم المرايا‬
Katakuri, it's me.
‫هذا أنا يا كاتاكوري‬
You managed to survive, Brother Peros.
‫لقد نجوت يا أخي بيروس‬
Yes, barely.
‫بأعجوبة‬
That bastard Pedro...
‫...يا لها من نهاية سخيفة وبائسة‬
died so pathetically!
‫انتهى بها بيدرو ذاك‬
Straw Hat! You were there, weren't you?
‫قبعة القش، شاهدت ذلك أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟‬
I suppose he sacrificed his life to try and kill me,
‫يبدو أنّه أراد قتلي عبر التضحية بحياته التافهة‬
but I'm very much alive, as you can probably tell.
‫لكنني ما زلتُ حيًّا أُرزق كما تسمع‬
So he died for no reason! Right?!
‫مما يعني أنّ تضحيته ذهبت هباءً، صحيح؟‬
Why don't you let him kill you already? Lick.
‫لذا لِمَ لا تستسلم ببساطة-بيرورين؟‬
What happened to Straw Hat's friends?
‫ماذا حدث لأتباع قبعة القش؟‬
Believe it or not,
‫لقد طاروا بسفينتهم عبر السماء وهربوا من حصارنا‬
I'm chasing them with Mama now...
‫إنني أطاردهم حاليًّا برفقة ماما‬
We're walking on the water.
‫نحن نسير على الماء‬
They're tenaciously trying to flee, but we'll catch up to them soon.
‫إنّهم يحاولون جاهدين الهرب، لكننا سنمسك بهم قريبًا‬
Amande and the others' fleet will be here soon, too.
‫سيصل أسطول أماند وبقية الأساطيل قريبًا أيضًا‬
I see.
‫فهمت‬
Brûlée.
‫بروليه‬
Ah, Big Brother...
‫أجل، أخي‬
How long do you plan on sleeping? Our soldiers can't go anywhere if you keep doing that.
‫إلى متى تنوين النوم؟ فجنودنا لا يسعهم الذهاب لأيّ مكان أثناء نومك‬
Okay.
‫أجل‬
I thought he might have been able to protect his crew with all of that vigor he's got,
‫حسبته أنقذ طاقمه عبر قراره الشجاع لكن اتضح أنّ هذا هو حال قبطانهم‬
Take those soldiers and go set fire or something to Straw Hat's ship.
‫خذي الجنود وأضرمي النيران في سفينة قبعة القش‬
Okay!
‫مفهوم‬
Big Sister Brûlée!
‫أختي بروليه‬
We found a mirror that goes to Straw Hat's ship!
‫وجدنا مرآة تؤدي إلى سفينة قبعة القش‬
Mascarpone 34th Son of the Charlotte Family Joscarpone 29th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
‫الابنة 29 لعائلة شارلوت جوسكربوني‬ ‫الابن 34 لعائلة شارلوت ماسكربوني‬
There must be one or two more!
‫لا بدّ من وجود واحدة أو أكثر غيرها‬
All right! Let's shoot flaming arrows at Straw Hat's ship!
‫عظيم، لنطلق سهامًا نارية في سفينة قبعة القش‬
I hope they're taken out by Mama while in a frenzy from the fire.
‫وبينما هم منهمكين بإخماد النيران، ستقضي عليهم ماما‬
Yikes!
‫كان ذلك وشيكًا‬
Give me that mirror!
‫سلّموني المرآة‬
Leave them alone!
‫دعوهم وشأنهم‬
I thought you wanted to have a one-on-one duel with me, Straw Hat.
‫ظننتُ أننا نخوض مواجهة فردية يا قبعة القش‬
That's what you get!
‫تستحق ذلك‬
Now, burn down Straw Hat's ship!
‫والآن، أحرقوا سفينة طاقم قبعة القش برمتها‬
Roger!
‫عُلم‬
Are you ready, Joscar?
‫هل أنتِ مستعدة يا جوسكر؟‬
I am, Mascar.
‫أنا مستعدة يا ماسكر‬
Now, shoot them!
‫الآن، أطلقا‬
Stop!!
‫توقفوا‬
No, you stop.
‫...إيّاك‬
A mirror!
‫مرآة‬
Hey, Nami!
‫يا نامي‬
Jinbe, can you hear me?!
‫جينبي، أتسمعني؟‬
Somebody, respond!
‫ليجب أحدٌ ما‬
At Sea, Totto Land
‫في البحر - توتولاند‬
Hey! Can you hear me?! Somebody!
‫أنتم، أيسمعني أحدكم؟‬
What? Luffy?!
‫لوفي؟‬
Nami!
‫نامي‬
Luffy, it's me! Are you okay?!
‫لوفي، هذه أنا، أأنت بخير؟‬
There are still some mirrors on the ship, right?!
‫ما زال يوجد بعض المرايا في السفينة، أليس كذلك؟‬
Maybe in the mens' bedroom or the bathroom?!
‫ربما في غرفة الرجال أو الحمام؟‬
It's burning up!
‫إنّها تحترق‬
We're gonna shoot, Joscar.
‫لنطلق النار يا جوسكر‬
Yes, we are, Mascar.
‫لنحرقها يا ماسكر‬
It's burning! It's burning!
‫إنّها تحترق، تحترق‬
Luffy?! What'd you say about mirrors?!
‫لوفي، ماذا بشأن المرايا؟‬
Break them all! To pieces!
‫حطمي جميعها إلى أشلاء‬
Are you out of your mind?! How will you come back if we do that?!
‫عمّ تتحدث؟ كيف ستعود إذًا؟‬
I don't know, but I'll be fine!
‫لا أعرف، لكنني سأجد طريقة‬
I'll figure something out!
‫سأتوصل إلى حلٍّ ما‬
I smell something!
‫أشمّ رائحة ما‬
I don't have a nose, though!
‫رغم أنني لا أملك أنفًا‬
The bathroom is on fire!
‫إنّ الغرفة تحترق‬
What's wrong?!
‫ما الخطب؟‬
How is this happening?!
‫ما الذي حدث؟‬
Flaming arrows from inside the mirror! Cannon shots from behind!
‫سهامٌ نارية من المرآة، وطلقات المدافع من خلفنا‬
One thing after the other! My eyes are spinning!
‫المصائب تصبُّ علينا، عيناي تدوران‬
Oh, I don't have eyes that can spin!
‫رغم أنني لا أملك عينين‬
In any case, let's put it out, Brook!
‫على أي حال، لنخمد النيران يا بروك‬
Now, you guys, keep shooting!
‫هيّا، لم ينتهِ عملكما بعد‬
We're gonna keep shooting, Joscar.
‫سنواصل إطلاق السهام النارية يا جوسكر‬
Yes, we are, Mascar.
‫لم ننتهِ بعد يا ماسكر‬
Stop it, you bastards!
‫توقفوا أيها الأوغاد‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي‬
Luffy! Are you okay?!
‫لوفي، أأنت بخير؟‬
Those of you who'll march onto the ship, follow me!
‫ليتبعني المكلّفين باقتحام السفينة‬
Oh, no!
‫هذا سيئ‬
Nami! Hurry up and break the mirrors! All of them!
‫نامي، حطّمي جميع المرايا بسرعة‬
But...
‫...ولكن‬
Our enemies are sending an army your way! I can't stop them by myself!
‫جيش العدو في طريقه نحوكم، لا يمكنني ردعهم وحدي‬
Let me focus just on this guy!
‫لذا دعوني أركز على هذا الشخص فقط‬
Nami! We have a problem!
‫نامي، نحن في ورطة‬
We can't get away!
‫لا يمكننا الهرب‬
A high wave!
‫...موجة عالية‬
Are you there...?
‫أتسمعني؟‬
I'm sorry, Luffy...
‫...المعذرة يا لوفي‬
I won't let you get away!
‫لن أدعكم تهربون‬
Nami! What's wrong?!
‫نامي، ما الخطب؟‬
might be done for...
‫ربما حانت نهايتنا‬